{
  "results": [
        {
      "question": "The number of holes in a stipulated round of golf",
      "correct_answer": 1,
      "option1": 18,
      "option2": 5,
      "option3": 7,
      "option4": 9
    },
    {
      "question":  "The minimum wind speed (mph) needed to issue a Severe Thunderstorm Warning",
      "correct_answer": 3,
      "option1": 68,
      "option2": 79,
      "option3": 58,
      "option4": 99
    },
    {
     
      "question": "The number of times an average person laughs a day",
      "correct_answer": 2,
      "option1": 10,
      "option2": 15,
      "option3": 25,
      "option4": 32
    },
    
    {
     
      "question": "The number of personality types in the Myers-Briggs classification system",
       "correct_answer": 2,
      "option1": 18,
      "option2": 16,
      "option3": 20,
      "option4": 10
    },
    {
    
      "question": "The minimum driving age for a car or van in the United Kingdom",
       "correct_answer": 1,
      "option1": 17,
      "option2": 18,
      "option3": 19,
      "option4": 21
    },
    {
      
      "question": "The number of Oscar nominations of actress Meryl Streep, who holds the record for the most Oscar nominated actress",
       "correct_answer": 1,
      "option1": 13,
      "option2": 9,
      "option3": 10,
      "option4": 15
    },
    {
      
      "question": "The number of times that a typical dairy cow lies down and stands up a day on average",
      "correct_answer": 3,
      "option1": 18,
      "option2": 5,
      "option3": 14,
      "option4": 9
    },
    {
      
      "question": "The number of colors the labels for Crayola crayons come in",
       "correct_answer": 2,
      "option1": 16,
      "option2": 18,
      "option3": 12,
      "option4": 9
    },
    {
      
      "question": "The number of questions in the popular party game Twenty Questions",
      "correct_answer": 1,
      "option1": 20,
      "option2": 50,
      "option3": 10,
      "option4": 40
    },
    {
      
      "question": "The number of days in a fortnight",
      "correct_answer": 3,
      "option1": 24,
      "option2": 4,
      "option3": 14,
      "option4": 24
    },
    {
      "question":  "The number of different characters that can be used with a standard English Keyboard, excluding uppercase letters",
      "correct_answer": 3,
      "option1": 32,
      "option2": 68,
      "option3": 71,
      "option4": 92
    },
    {
       "question":  "The number of unique ranks in a suit in a pack of cards.",
      "correct_answer": 2,
      "option1": 12,
      "option2": 13,
      "option3": 20,
      "option4": 14
    }

    
  ]
  
}
